Movie Poster and Associated Materials Collection, 1908-1977
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
Movie Poster and Associated Materials Collection, 1908-1977
MS 528
University of Arizona. Library. Special Collections
This is an artificial collection comprised motion picture posters and related materials which include press kits film scripts, and still photographs, and advertisements for western goods and depictions of western life in the 20th century. Motion pictures filmed in the American Southwest is the central theme to the majority of the materials.
30 Linear feet
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL: http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/
Restrictions
There are no restrictions on this collection.
Accruals
Future accretions to the collection are expected.
Historical Note
In the early 20th century, movie studios used the poster as a commercial tool to publicize a movie and draw audiences into theaters because they were mobile, conveyed an immediate and understandable message to mass audiences, and were cheap to produce. Posters created during this period were lithographs on cheap paper, and subsequently few examples from the early period of film history survive today and the ones that do are usually in poor condition. Between the 1930's-1940's Hollywood studios printed approximately 7,000-20,000 posters per movie, depending on the promotional budget for the film. Usually studios rented or sold posters to exhibitors for a minimal fee who displayed them in theaters. Exhibitors employed frames to display posters which lead to creating standard sizes for posters which included one-sheets, half-sheets, three-sheets, inserts, and lobby cards. Between 1940's to the mid-1980's, most major studios handed the production and distribution of all movie paper advertising to the National Screen Service (NSS ) which distributed an estimated 90 percent of movie posters in the United States. By the mid 1980's movie theaters with individual screens were replaced by multiplex theaters which used multiple theaters to screen a variety of films. Promotion of individual films gave way to promotion of multiple films in a limited space. This resulted in the phasing out of various sizes of movie posters including half-sheets, three-sheets, inserts, and lobby cards.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into 8 series.
Series I: Mounted Movie and Americana Posters, 1908 – 1958
Series II: Standard Size Movie Posters, 1936-1987 (bulk 1948-1972)
Series III: Oversize Movie Posters, 1936-1987 (bulk 1948-1972)
Series IV: Movie Press Books, 1936-1976
Series V: Lobby Cards, 1928-1973
Series VI: Still Photographs, 1950 – 1977
Series VI: Miniature Posters, undated
Series VI: Scripts, 1938, 1950
Scope and Content Note
This is an artificial collection. The collection has eight series and contains movie posters, lobby cards, promotional still photographs, press books, and scripts relating to movies produced by American Film companies that were filmed in Southern Arizona, more specifically Old Tucson, or were set in the American Southwest. The collection also contains posters of advertisements of western goods and depictions of western life in the 20th century. Many of the movies are from the western genre from the late 1940's – 1960's, but the biker, film noir, science fiction, and thriller genres are also represented. Some of the posters and other associated material were part of the international distribution of films and come from Spain, Belgium, France, Germany, England, Mexico, and Denmark. Most traditional promotional poster sizes are represented including one sheets (27x41"), half sheets (22x28"), insert cards (14x36"), and window cards (14x22"). Materials are in English, French, Spanish, German, and Danish.
Access Terms
Film posters.
Film posters – Specimens.
Motion picture plays.
Film stills--1950-1960.
Film stills--1960-1970.
Film stills--1970-1980.
Advertising--United States--Posters.
Container List
- Series 1: Mounted Movie and Americana Posters, 1908 – 1958
  This series contains posters that are mounted on canvas as well as posters that are shrink wrapped with foam core. This series includes movie posters and two advertisements of depictions of western life in the 20th century. All posters are one sheet in size (27x41").
  - Misc. Western Posters – Stetson (hat) advertisement, undated (Drawer 5, Folder 1)
  - Misc. Western Posters – Mail Pouch Tobacco advertisement depicting the Arizona Camel Corps, undated (Drawer 5, Folder 1)
  - Arizona, 1908; Canvas Backed (Drawer 5, Folder 1)
  - Arizona Frontier, 1940; Canvas Backed (Drawer 5, Folder 1)
  - Arizona Stage Coach, 1942; Canvas Backed (Drawer 5, Folder 1)
  - Montana Frank Shows, 1910; Canvas Backed (Drawer 5, Folder 1)
  - Santa Fe Railroad Posters "Indian Detours, On the Way to or from California", undated; Shrink Wrapped with Foam Core (Drawer 5, Folder 1)
  - The Arizona Cowboy, 1948; Shrink Wrapped with Foam Core (Drawer 5, Folder 1)
  - Gunsmoke in Tucson, 1958; Shrink Wrapped with Foam Core (Drawer 5, Folder 1)
  - Jesse James the Missouri Outlaw, undated; Shrink Wrapped with Foam Core (Drawer 5, Folder 1)
  - A Texas Ranger, undated; Shrink Wrapped with Foam Core (Drawer 5, Folder 1)
  - The Wildcat of Tucson, 1940; Shrink Wrapped with Foam Core (Drawer 5, Folder 1)
- Series 2: Standard Size Movie Posters, 1936-1987 (bulk 1948-1972)
  This series is arranged alphabetically by film title and contains standard size movie posters that are not mounted on canvas or foam core. Movie posters contained within the series come in various and sometimes multiple sizes. Sizes included are one sheet (27x41"), half sheet (22x28"), insert card (14x36"), window card (14x22"). The container list denotes poster style. Materials are primarily in English, with some titles in Spain, Italy, Belgium, Danish, and German. Posters with foreign titles are listed under the American title when determined.
  - 3 on a Couch, 1966; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 1)
  - 7 Men from Now, 1966; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 1)
  - 40 Guns to Apache Pass (40 Fusils Manquent a l'Appel), Belgium, 1966; window card (Drawer 6, Folder 1)
  - 100 Rifles (les 100 Fusils), Belgium, 1969; window card (Drawer 6, Folder 1)
  - 100 Rifles, 1969; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 1)
  - Alvarez Kelly, 1966; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 1)
  - The Animals, 1971; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 1)
  - Apache Ambush, 1955; insert card (Drawer 6, Folder 1)
  - Apache Drums, 1951; half sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 1)
  - Apache Kid (Kampen I Dodspasset), Danish, 1941; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 1)
  - Apache Rifles (Furie Apache), Belgium, 1964; window card (Drawer 6, Folder 1)
  - Apache Territory, 1958; half sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 1)
  - Apache Territory (El Oasis Maldito), Spain, 1958; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 1)
  - Apache Uprising, 1965; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 1)
  - Apache War Smoke, 1952; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 1)
  - Apache Warrior, 1957; half sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 1)
  - Apache Warrior, 1957; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 1)
  - Apache’s Last Battle, 1964; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 1)
  - The Appaloosa, 1966; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 1)
  - Arena (L’Arene), Belgium, 1953; insert card (Drawer 6, Folder 1)
  - Arena, 1953; window card (Drawer 6, Folder 1)
  - Arena(2 copies), 1953; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 1)
  - Arizona Bushwackers (Les Rebelles de L’Arizona / Opstand in Arizona), 1967; window card (Drawer 6, Folder 1)
  - Arizona Bushwackers, 1967; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 1)
  - Arizona Colt, Belgium, 1966; window card (Drawer 6, Folder 1)
  - Arizona Cowboy, 1949; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 1)
  - Arizona Gang Busters, 1940; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 1)
  - Arizona Manhunt, 1951; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 1)
  - The Arizona Raiders, 1936; window card (Drawer 6, Folder 1)
  - Arizona Raiders, 1965; half sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 1)
  - Arizona Raiders(2 copies), 1965; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 1)
  - The Arizona Ranger, 1948; half sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 1)
  - The Arizona Ranger, 1948; insert card (Drawer 6, Folder 1)
  - The Arizona Ranger, 1948; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 1)
  - The Arizonian (re-release), 1951; insert card (Drawer 6, Folder 1)
  - Bad Company, 1972; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 2)
  - The Badlanders, 1958; insert card (Drawer 6, Folder 2)
  - The Badlanders, 1958; half sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 2)
  - The Badlanders, 1958; half sheet version 2 (Drawer 6, Folder 2)
  - The Badlanders, 1958; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 2)
  - Bandolero!, 1968; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 2)
  - Barquero, France, 1970; window card (Drawer 6, Folder 2)
  - Barquero, France, 1970; half sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 2)
  - Barquero, 1970; half sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 2)
  - Barquero, 1970; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 2)
  - The Big Gundown, 1968; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 2)
  - Billy Jack, 1971; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 2)
  - Born Losers, 1967; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 2)
  - Born Losers (re-release), 1967; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 2)
  - Born to Kill, 1947; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 2)
  - Both Barrels Blazing, 1945; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 2)
  - The Bottom of the Bottle, 1956; insert card (Drawer 6, Folder 2)
  - The Bottom of the Bottle, 1956; insert card (Drawer 6, Folder 2)
  - The Bounty Killer, 1965; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 2)
  - The Bravados, 1958; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 2)
  - Bronco Billy, 1980; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 2)
  - Buck and the Preacher, 1972; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 2)
  - Buffalo Stampede, 1950; half sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 2)
  - Cancel My Reservation, 1972; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 3)
  - Captain Apache, 1972; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 3)
  - Cariboo Trail (Camino Virgen), Spain, 1950; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 3)
  - The Challenge of Rin-Tin-Tin (El Desafio de Rin-Tin-Tin), Spain, 1958; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 3)
  - Chato’s Land, 1972; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 3)
  - Cheyenne Autumn (Les Cheyennes), France, 1964; half sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 3)
  - Coogan’s Bluff, 1968; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 3)
  - Coroner Creek (Aguas Sangrientas), Spain, 1948; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 3)
  - Cotter, 1973; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 3)
  - Cry Blood, Apache, 1970; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 3)
  - The Day it Came to Earth, Style B, 1977; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 4)
  - Day of the Badman, 1958; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 4)
  - Day of the Evil Gun, 1968; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 4)
  - A Day of Fury, 1958; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 4)
  - The Deadly Companions, 1961; insert card (Drawer 6, Folder 4)
  - The Deadly Companions (Les Compagnons de la Mort), Belgium, 1961; window card (Drawer 6, Folder 4)
  - The Deadly Companions, 1961; half sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 4)
  - The Deadly Companions,Style A, 1961; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 4)
  - The Deadly Companions,Style B, 1961; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 4)
  - Death of a Gunfighter, 1969; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 4)
  - The Desert Horseman (El Fantasma del Desierto), Spain, 1946; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 4)
  - The Desperado Trail, 1966; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 4)
  - The Desperados, 1969; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 4)
  - Devil’s Canyon (Nuit Sauvage), Belgium, 1953; window card (Drawer 6, Folder 4)
  - Devil’s Canyon, 1953; half sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 4)
  - A Distant Trumpet, 1964; insert card (Drawer 6, Folder 4)
  - Doc, style A, 1971; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 4)
  - Doc, style B, 1971; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 4)
  - Duel at Apache Wells, Style B, 1957; half sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 4)
  - Duel at Diablo, 1966; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 4)
  - Escape from Fort Bravo, 1953; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 5)
  - An Eye for an Eye, 1966; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 5)
  - Face to Face, (Il etait Une Fois en Arizona), Belgium, 1967; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 5)
  - Finger on the Trigger, 1965; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 5)
  - Firecreek (Les 5 Hors La Loi), France, 1968; half sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 5)
  - Firecreek, 1968; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 5)
  - Five Bloody Graves, 1970; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 5)
  - Fort Courageous, 1965; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 5)
  - Fort Yuma (Belgium), 1954; window card (Drawer 6, Folder 5)
  - Fort Yuma, 1954; insert card (Drawer 6, Folder 5)
  - Fort Yuma, 1954; half sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 5)
  - Fort Yuma Gold (Trois Cavaliers Pour Fort Yuma), France, 1966; insert card (Drawer 6, Folder 5)
  - Four Rode Out, 1969; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 5)
  - Frontier Gun, 1958; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 5)
  - Frontier Hellcat, (Parmi Les Vautours De Gang der Aasgieren), Belgium, 1966; window card (Drawer 6, Folder 5)
  - Frontier Hellcat, 1966; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 5)
  - Frontier Scout, 1956; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 5)
  - Fury at Gunsight Pass, 1956; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 5)
  - The Gentleman from Arizona (Le Gentleman de l’ Arizona), Belgium, 1939; window card (Drawer 6, Folder 6)
  - Geronimo, Belgium, Style A, 1939; window card (Drawer 6, Folder 6)
  - Geronimo, (Geronimo le Peau-Rouge), Belgium, 1939; window card (Drawer 6, Folder 6)
  - Get Mean, 1975; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 6)
  - Gun Fury (2 copies), 1953; insert card (Drawer 6, Folder 6)
  - Gun Fury, 1953; half sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 6)
  - A Gunfight, 1971; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 6)
  - Gunfight at O.K. Corral (Defi a Geweervuur te O.K. Corral), Belgium, 1970; insert card (Drawer 6, Folder 6)
  - Gunfight at O.K. Corral, 1970; insert card (Drawer 6, Folder 6)
  - Guns of Hate, 1948; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 6)
  - Gunslingers, Spain, 1950; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 6)
  - Gunsmoke in Tucson (Les Pillards de L’Arizona), Belgium, 1958; window card (Drawer 6, Folder 6)
  - Gunsmoke in Tucson, 1958; insert card (Drawer 6, Folder 6)
  - Gunsmoke in Tucson, 1958; half sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 6)
  - Hanger 18, 1980; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 7)
  - Hawk of Wild River (el Gavilan del Oeste), Spain, 1952; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 7)
  - Hombre, United Kingdom, 1967; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 7)
  - The Honkers, 1972; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 7)
  - Hostile Guns, 1967; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 7)
  - Hour of the Gun (7 Seconds es en Enfer, 7 Sekonden in Hel), France, 1967; window card (Drawer 6, Folder 7)
  - Hour of the Gun (7 Secondes en Enfer), France, 1967; half sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 7)
  - How the West Was Won (La Conquete de L’Quest), France, 1964; window card (Drawer 6, Folder 7)
  - How the West Was Won, 1964; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 7)
  - Incident at Phantom Hill (2 copies), 1965; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 7)
  - The Iron Sheriff, 1957; insert card (Drawer 6, Folder 7)
  - The Iron Sheriff, 1957; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 7)
  - It Came from Outer Space (Les Inconnus D’un Autre Monde), Belgium, 1953; window card (Drawer 6, Folder 7)
  - J.W. Coop, 1972; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 7)
  - Jack Slade, Style A, 1953; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 7)
  - Johnny Concho, 1956; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 7)
  - Johnny Tiger, 1966; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 7)
  - Junior Bonner, Style B, 1972; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 7)
  - Land Beyond the Law (Tierra Sin Ley), Re-release, Spain, 1937; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 8)
  - Land Raiders (L’Quest en Feu), Belgium, 1969; window card (Drawer 6, Folder 8)
  - Land Raiders, 1969; one sheet (landscape) (Drawer 6, Folder 8)
  - Land Raiders, 1969; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 8)
  - Landrush, 1946; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 8)
  - The Last Hard Men, 1976; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 8)
  - The Last Wagon, 1956; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 8)
  - Lawman (2 copies), 1971; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 8)
  - Little Fauss and Big Halsy (Petit Fauss et Grand Halsy), Belgium, 1970; window card (Drawer 6, Folder 8)
  - Little Fauss and Big Halsy (2 copies), 1971; one sheet (Drawer 6, Folder 8)
  - The Long Ride Home (La Sanglante Chevauchee), Belgium, 1967; window card (Drawer 6, Folder 8)
  - Mackenna’s Gold (Het Goud Van Mackenna), Belgium, 1969; window card (Drawer 7, Folder 1)
  - Mackenna’s Gold, 1969; window card (Drawer 7, Folder 1)
  - The McMasters, 1970; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 1)
  - Mad Dog, undated; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 1)
  - Man and Boy, 1971; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 1)
  - The Man From Nowhere, 1968; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 1)
  - The Master Gunfighter, 1975; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 1)
  - The Master Gunfighter, Style B, 1975; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 1)
  - The Maverick Queen, 1956; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 1)
  - The Meanest Men in the West, 1978; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 1)
  - Meet in the Heat of Fire Creek, 1967; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 1)
  - Money, Women and Guns, 1958; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 1)
  - More Dead Than Alive (Meer Dood Dan Levend), Belgium, 1968; window card (Drawer 7, Folder 1)
  - More Dead Than Alive, 1968; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 1)
  - No Name on the Bullet, 1959; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 1)
  - One Big Affair, 1959; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 2)
  - One Foot in Hell, 1960; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 2)
  - Orlando, Trinidad, undated; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 2)
  - Outlaw Women, 1956; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 2)
  - Outrage, 1950; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 2)
  - Pat Garrett and Billy the Kid, 1973; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 2)
  - P.J., 1968; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 2)
  - Powder River Rustlers, 1949; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 2)
  - The Proud and the Damned, 1972; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 2)
  - The Purple Hills, 1961; insert card (Drawer 7, Folder 2)
  - The Purple Hills, 1961; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 2)
  - The Quick Gun, 1964; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 3)
  - The Raid, 1954; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 3)
  - Raising Arizona, 1987; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 3)
  - Ransom!, 1956; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 3)
  - The Redhead and the Cowboy, 1951; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 3)
  - Renegades of the Sage, 1949; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 3)
  - Requiem for a Gunfighter (2 copies), 1965; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 3)
  - Return of the Gunfighter (Le Justicier de L’Arizona), Belgium, 1967; window card (Drawer 7, Folder 3)
  - The Reward, Style B, 1965; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 3)
  - Ride a Violent Mile, 1957; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 3)
  - The Ride Back, 1957; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 3)
  - Ride Beyond Vengeance (2 copies), 1966; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 3)
  - Ride the Man Down, 1952; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 3)
  - The Ride to Hangman’s Tree, 1967; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 3)
  - Rider from Tucson, 1950; insert card (Drawer 7, Folder 3)
  - Rio Conchos, 1964; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 3)
  - Robbers Roost, 1955; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 3)
  - The Rounders, 1965; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 3)
  - Sabata, 1970; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 4)
  - Sand (Gritos en la Sierra), Spain, 1949; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 4)
  - Sand (Gritos en la Sierra), Spain, 1949; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 4)
  - The Savage Guns, 1962; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 4)
  - The Scalphunters, 1968; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 4)
  - The Second Time Around, 1961; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 4)
  - Shadows of Tombstone, 1953; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 4)
  - The Shakiest Gun in the West, 1968; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 4)
  - Shoot Out, 1971; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 4)
  - Showdown, H Version, 1973; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 4)
  - The Silencers (Les Tueuses), Belgium, 1966; window card (Drawer 7, Folder 4)
  - The Silencers, 1966; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 4)
  - The Silver Whip, 1953; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 4)
  - Stage to Thunder Rock, 1963; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 4)
  - Stage to Tucson (Les Ecumeurs Des Monts Apaches), Belgium, 1950; window card (Drawer 7, Folder 4)
  - Stage to Tucson, 1950; insert card (Drawer 7, Folder 4)
  - Stagecoach to Dancer’s Rock, 1962; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 4)
  - Stagecoach to Fury, 1956; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 4)
  - Stampede (Rivalite en Arizona), Belgium, 1950; window card (Drawer 7, Folder 4)
  - Stars in my Crown, 1950; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 4)
  - Stay Away, Joe (Mic-Mac Montana), Belgium, 1968; window card (Drawer 7, Folder 4)
  - The Storm Rider, 1957; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 4)
  - A Stranger in Town, 1968; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 4)
  - The Stranger Returns, 1968; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 4)
  - Support Your Local Gunfighter, 1971; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 4)
  - Support Your Local Sheriff, 1969; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 4)
  - Taggart, 1964; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 5)
  - There was a Crooked Man (Zwei Dreckige Halunken), German, 1961; half sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 5)
  - There was a Crooked Man (Le Reptile), France, 1961; half sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 5)
  - This Side of the Law, 1961; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 5)
  - 3:10 to Yuma (3H.10 Pour Yuma), Belgium, 1957; window card (Drawer 7, Folder 5)
  - Three Young Texans, 1954; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 5)
  - Thunder in the Sun, 1959; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 5)
  - Thunder Mountain, 1947; insert card (Drawer 7, Folder 5)
  - A Thunder of Drums (Tonnerre Apache), Belgium, 1961; window card (Drawer 7, Folder 5)
  - A Thunder of Drums, 1961; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 5)
  - Today We Kill…Tomorrow We Die!, 1971; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 5)
  - Toughest Man in Arizona (Le Sherrif de Tombstone), Belgium, 1952; window card (Drawer 7, Folder 5)
  - Toughest Man in Arizona, 1952; insert card (Drawer 7, Folder 5)
  - Toughest Man in Arizona, 1952; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 5)
  - Town Tamer, 1965; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 5)
  - Track the Man Down, 1955; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 5)
  - Trail of the Rustlers, 1949; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 5)
  - Train to Tombstone, 1950; insert card (Drawer 7, Folder 5)
  - Train to Tombstone, 1950; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 5)
  - The Tramplers, 1966; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 5)
  - Tucson, 1948; half sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 5)
  - Tucson, 1948; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 5)
  - The Ugly Ones, 1968; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 6)
  - Ulzana’s Raid, 1972; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 6)
  - Under Arizona Skies (2 copies), 1946; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 6)
  - Valdez is Coming, 1971; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 6)
  - Wake me When It’s Over, 1960; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 6)
  - Walk the Proud Land (Terre D’Aventure), Belgium, 1956; window card (Drawer 7, Folder 6)
  - Walk the Proud Land, 1956; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 6)
  - Walk the Proud Land, 1956; one sheet (landscape) (Drawer 7, Folder 6)
  - War Drums, 1957; one sheet (landscape) (Drawer 7, Folder 6)
  - Welcome to Hard Times, 1967; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 6)
  - What Ever Happened to Aunt Alice?, 1969; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 6)
  - Where Angels Go…Trouble Follows, Australia, 1968; insert card (Drawer 7, Folder 6)
  - Where Angels Go…Trouble Follows (Les Gamines Explosives), Belgium, 1968; window card (Drawer 7, Folder 6)
  - The Wild and the Innocent, 1959; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 6)
  - The Wildcat of Tucson, 1940; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 6)
  - Young Fury, 1965; one sheet (Drawer 7, Folder 6)
- Series 3: Oversize Movie Posters, 1937-1967
  This series is arranged alphabetically by film title and contains oversize posters. Poster sizes represented in this series include two sheet (41"x81"), three sheet (81" x 81"), and six sheet (three sheets of 81" x 81"). Posters with a foreign title are listed under the American title when determined.
  - Apache Drums, 1951; 3 sheet (Drawer oversize 2, Folder 1)
  - Apache Gold, style A, 1965; 3 sheet (Drawer oversize 2, Folder 1)
  - Apache Gold, style B, 1965; 3 sheet (Drawer oversize 2, Folder 1)
  - Apache Rifles, 1964; 6 sheet (Drawer oversize 2, Folder 1)
  - Apace War Smoke, 1952; 3 sheet (Drawer oversize 2, Folder 1)
  - Arena, 1953; 3 sheet (Drawer oversize 2, Folder 1)